{
    "subject": "resource/Born_in_East_L.A._(song)",
    "predicate": "ontology/musicalBand",
    "object": "resource/Cheech_&_Chong",
    "human_readable": "The song 'Born in East L.A.' is performed by Cheech & Chong.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9687709212303162,
            "question": "Who performs the song 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9672969579696655,
            "question": "Did Cheech & Chong write the song 'Born in East L.A.' themselves?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9036398530006409,
            "question": "What is the title of the song performed by Cheech & Chong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8928065896034241,
            "question": "Is 'Born in East L.A.' a popular song?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7911285161972046,
            "question": "What is the overall theme of the song 'Born in East L.A.'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.573494017124176,
            "question": "Where was Cheech & Chong's music primarily popular?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5709394812583923,
            "question": "What genre of music is associated with Cheech & Chong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4511295258998871,
            "question": "Has 'Born in East L.A.' been featured in any movies or TV shows?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4251822233200073,
            "question": "What other songs are popular among Cheech & Chong's discography?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3172209858894348,
            "question": "Are Cheech & Chong known for any particular style of humor?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The song 'Born in East L.A.' is performed by Cheech & Chong.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3662_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other songs are popular among Cheech & Chong's discography?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3662_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has 'Born in East L.A.' been featured in any movies or TV shows?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3662_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is associated with Cheech & Chong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3662_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3662_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement that the song \"Born in East L.A.\" is performed by Cheech & Chong. For example, the document at `/Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3662/re-ranker-msmarco/88.txt` mentions it as a song from an album, and other documents indicate that Cheech Marin wrote, directed, and starred in a film based on the song."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}